{"qid": "hard-coffee-0000", "question": "What was the highest coffee price from 2009-12-23 to 2019-05-10?", "answer": "306.25 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0001", "question": "What was the highest coffee price from 2010-03-26 to 2014-05-15?", "answer": "306.25 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0002", "question": "What was the highest coffee price from 2009-04-28 to 2021-10-14?", "answer": "306.25 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0003", "question": "What was the highest coffee price from 2008-02-28 to 2020-07-08?", "answer": "306.25 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0004", "question": "What was the highest coffee price from 2004-10-13 to 2018-12-21?", "answer": "306.25 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0005", "question": "What was the highest coffee price from 2022-06-22 to 2022-08-16?", "answer": "237.1 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0006", "question": "What was the highest coffee price from 2000-10-25 to 2012-10-17?", "answer": "306.25 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0007", "question": "What was the highest coffee price from 2010-03-09 to 2010-07-15?", "answer": "175.0 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0008", "question": "What was the highest coffee price from 2017-10-20 to 2020-04-23?", "answer": "138.4 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0009", "question": "What was the highest coffee price from 2009-09-01 to 2012-06-21?", "answer": "306.25 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0010", "question": "What was the lowest coffee price from 2013-07-29 to 2018-12-04?", "answer": "92.0 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0011", "question": "What was the lowest coffee price from 2020-03-04 to 2021-11-03?", "answer": "92.7 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0012", "question": "What was the lowest coffee price from 2008-05-21 to 2016-06-24?", "answer": "100.95 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0013", "question": "What was the lowest coffee price from 2002-04-25 to 2012-10-01?", "answer": "46.0 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0014", "question": "What was the lowest coffee price from 2020-06-03 to 2022-01-20?", "answer": "92.7 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0015", "question": "What was the lowest coffee price from 2005-07-14 to 2014-04-23?", "answer": "87.5 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0016", "question": "What was the lowest coffee price from 2001-04-23 to 2015-12-02?", "answer": "41.5 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0017", "question": "What was the lowest coffee price from 2014-08-19 to 2019-03-28?", "answer": "92.0 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0018", "question": "What was the lowest coffee price from 2018-10-30 to 2021-02-11?", "answer": "86.35 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0019", "question": "What was the lowest coffee price from 2009-11-25 to 2021-11-29?", "answer": "86.35 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0020", "question": "What was the average coffee price from 2018-05-22 to 2021-01-08?", "answer": "106.7 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0021", "question": "What was the average coffee price from 2009-10-21 to 2021-10-07?", "answer": "148.1 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0022", "question": "What was the average coffee price from 2016-10-24 to 2019-03-29?", "answer": "122.6 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0023", "question": "What was the average coffee price from 2003-02-21 to 2010-03-16?", "answer": "105.9 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0024", "question": "What was the average coffee price from 2001-04-19 to 2010-08-22?", "answer": "98.1 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0025", "question": "What was the average coffee price from 2004-11-09 to 2019-10-11?", "answer": "140.5 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0026", "question": "What was the average coffee price from 2008-12-30 to 2015-05-29?", "answer": "168.7 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0027", "question": "What was the average coffee price from 2000-03-15 to 2007-03-16?", "answer": "79.0 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0028", "question": "What was the average coffee price from 2002-02-20 to 2005-09-08?", "answer": "73.8 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0029", "question": "What was the average coffee price from 2013-12-30 to 2016-02-05?", "answer": "153.6 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0030", "question": "How much did the coffee price change from 2017-08-16 to 2019-06-19?", "answer": "-36.6 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0031", "question": "How much did the coffee price change from 2018-03-21 to 2022-07-25?", "answer": "91.5 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0032", "question": "How much did the coffee price change from 2007-06-18 to 2018-09-26?", "answer": "-16.8 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0033", "question": "How much did the coffee price change from 2019-11-21 to 2021-03-16?", "answer": "24.5 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0034", "question": "How much did the coffee price change from 2001-12-27 to 2021-02-12?", "answer": "74.7 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0035", "question": "How much did the coffee price change from 2014-12-21 to 2018-07-09?", "answer": "-62.7 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0036", "question": "How much did the coffee price change from 2020-12-28 to 2022-01-21?", "answer": "112.2 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0037", "question": "How much did the coffee price change from 2022-04-11 to 2022-07-11?", "answer": "-14.8 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0038", "question": "How much did the coffee price change from 2004-05-27 to 2020-01-29?", "answer": "22.2 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0039", "question": "How much did the coffee price change from 2015-09-04 to 2018-11-30?", "answer": "-13.2 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0040", "question": "What was the percentage change in coffee price on 2021-05-28 compared to the previous day?", "answer": "4.5%"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0041", "question": "What was the percentage change in coffee price on 2019-05-30 compared to the previous day?", "answer": "2.9%"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0042", "question": "What was the percentage change in coffee price on 2018-07-06 compared to the previous day?", "answer": "4.7%"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0043", "question": "What was the percentage change in coffee price on 2005-01-07 compared to the previous day?", "answer": "-0.6%"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0044", "question": "What was the percentage change in coffee price on 2003-07-11 compared to the previous day?", "answer": "0.3%"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0045", "question": "What was the percentage change in coffee price on 2018-01-08 compared to the previous day?", "answer": "-2.6%"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0046", "question": "What was the percentage change in coffee price on 2001-11-30 compared to the previous day?", "answer": "1.4%"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0047", "question": "What was the percentage change in coffee price on 2005-11-09 compared to the previous day?", "answer": "-0.9%"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0048", "question": "What was the percentage change in coffee price on 2000-04-14 compared to the previous day?", "answer": "-2.2%"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0049", "question": "What was the percentage change in coffee price on 2001-03-05 compared to the previous day?", "answer": "0.6%"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0050", "question": "On which date from 2016-10-14 to 2019-11-05 was the difference between the highest and lowest coffee prices the greatest?", "answer": "2016-11-10"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0051", "question": "On which date from 2004-02-02 to 2020-02-06 was the difference between the highest and lowest coffee prices the greatest?", "answer": "2014-02-19"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0052", "question": "On which date from 2012-09-25 to 2019-07-15 was the difference between the highest and lowest coffee prices the greatest?", "answer": "2014-02-19"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0053", "question": "On which date from 2012-05-11 to 2017-07-17 was the difference between the highest and lowest coffee prices the greatest?", "answer": "2014-02-19"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0054", "question": "On which date from 2017-10-27 to 2018-11-08 was the difference between the highest and lowest coffee prices the greatest?", "answer": "2018-10-29"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0055", "question": "On which date from 2005-04-21 to 2020-08-12 was the difference between the highest and lowest coffee prices the greatest?", "answer": "2014-02-19"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0056", "question": "On which date from 2014-05-30 to 2020-09-16 was the difference between the highest and lowest coffee prices the greatest?", "answer": "2014-10-06"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0057", "question": "On which date from 2015-05-01 to 2020-01-03 was the difference between the highest and lowest coffee prices the greatest?", "answer": "2016-06-09"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0058", "question": "On which date from 2021-11-04 to 2021-11-30 was the difference between the highest and lowest coffee prices the greatest?", "answer": "2021-11-29"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0059", "question": "On which date from 2014-04-16 to 2018-03-05 was the difference between the highest and lowest coffee prices the greatest?", "answer": "2014-10-06"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0060", "question": "What was the average daily volume of coffee traded from 2019-09-11 to 2022-01-26?", "answer": "13003.8"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0061", "question": "What was the average daily volume of coffee traded from 2002-03-28 to 2015-06-09?", "answer": "7358.8"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0062", "question": "What was the average daily volume of coffee traded from 2007-08-02 to 2009-08-26?", "answer": "7455.1"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0063", "question": "What was the average daily volume of coffee traded from 2006-04-20 to 2019-03-06?", "answer": "9322.4"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0064", "question": "What was the average daily volume of coffee traded from 2013-05-29 to 2013-09-19?", "answer": "8729.9"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0065", "question": "What was the average daily volume of coffee traded from 2018-09-06 to 2021-05-24?", "answer": "14088.0"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0066", "question": "What was the average daily volume of coffee traded from 2008-09-11 to 2014-07-30?", "answer": "7812.2"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0067", "question": "What was the average daily volume of coffee traded from 2011-10-25 to 2013-12-19?", "answer": "8534.1"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0068", "question": "What was the average daily volume of coffee traded from 2002-12-02 to 2003-09-04?", "answer": "4381.5"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0069", "question": "What was the average daily volume of coffee traded from 2020-08-24 to 2021-05-12?", "answer": "11236.8"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0070", "question": "On which date from 2017-07-05 to 2021-11-09 did the coffee price have the highest increase compared to the previous day?", "answer": "2021-07-26"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0071", "question": "On which date from 2019-05-03 to 2021-10-25 did the coffee price have the highest increase compared to the previous day?", "answer": "2021-07-26"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0072", "question": "On which date from 2016-01-26 to 2022-02-23 did the coffee price have the highest increase compared to the previous day?", "answer": "2021-07-26"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0073", "question": "On which date from 2016-03-02 to 2019-07-16 did the coffee price have the highest increase compared to the previous day?", "answer": "2016-06-08"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0074", "question": "On which date from 2019-10-15 to 2022-04-05 did the coffee price have the highest increase compared to the previous day?", "answer": "2021-07-26"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0075", "question": "On which date from 2022-02-18 to 2022-06-08 did the coffee price have the highest increase compared to the previous day?", "answer": "2022-05-11"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0076", "question": "On which date from 2015-09-28 to 2018-12-20 did the coffee price have the highest increase compared to the previous day?", "answer": "2016-06-08"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0077", "question": "On which date from 2000-01-11 to 2020-08-21 did the coffee price have the highest increase compared to the previous day?", "answer": "2014-02-19"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0078", "question": "On which date from 2014-07-15 to 2021-10-05 did the coffee price have the highest increase compared to the previous day?", "answer": "2021-07-26"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0079", "question": "On which date from 2004-05-06 to 2010-01-25 did the coffee price have the highest increase compared to the previous day?", "answer": "2004-11-15"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0080", "question": "How many times from 2009-06-26 to 2021-03-16 did the coffee price increase compared to the previous day?", "answer": "1491"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0081", "question": "How many times from 2009-07-20 to 2011-01-26 did the coffee price increase compared to the previous day?", "answer": "221"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0082", "question": "How many times from 2012-10-10 to 2019-06-27 did the coffee price increase compared to the previous day?", "answer": "835"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0083", "question": "How many times from 2012-11-30 to 2014-03-24 did the coffee price increase compared to the previous day?", "answer": "165"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0084", "question": "How many times from 2012-06-07 to 2017-11-16 did the coffee price increase compared to the previous day?", "answer": "688"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0085", "question": "How many times from 2009-12-13 to 2020-05-05 did the coffee price increase compared to the previous day?", "answer": "1319"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0086", "question": "How many times from 2002-10-18 to 2014-11-30 did the coffee price increase compared to the previous day?", "answer": "1561"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0087", "question": "How many times from 2000-02-25 to 2004-03-26 did the coffee price increase compared to the previous day?", "answer": "473"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0088", "question": "How many times from 2009-08-05 to 2012-02-01 did the coffee price increase compared to the previous day?", "answer": "343"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0089", "question": "How many times from 2021-11-17 to 2022-07-21 did the coffee price increase compared to the previous day?", "answer": "78"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0090", "question": "What was the percentage increase in coffee price from 2017-10-16 to 2022-06-23?", "answer": "81.6%"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0091", "question": "What was the percentage increase in coffee price from 2017-04-25 to 2020-07-24?", "answer": "-16.3%"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0092", "question": "What was the percentage increase in coffee price from 2016-05-26 to 2021-11-01?", "answer": "71.2%"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0093", "question": "What was the percentage increase in coffee price from 2022-03-28 to 2022-05-02?", "answer": "-2.4%"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0094", "question": "What was the percentage increase in coffee price from 2013-11-14 to 2015-09-17?", "answer": "10.1%"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0095", "question": "What was the percentage increase in coffee price from 2012-10-12 to 2014-04-08?", "answer": "22.0%"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0096", "question": "What was the percentage increase in coffee price from 2012-03-02 to 2014-09-26?", "answer": "-8.3%"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0097", "question": "What was the percentage increase in coffee price from 2011-08-11 to 2016-09-26?", "answer": "-34.7%"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0098", "question": "What was the percentage increase in coffee price from 2010-10-14 to 2012-01-20?", "answer": "21.0%"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0099", "question": "What was the percentage increase in coffee price from 2004-10-19 to 2014-12-22?", "answer": "134.7%"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0100", "question": "What was the coffee price range from 2000-01-03 to 2014-03-24?", "answer": "306.2 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0101", "question": "What was the coffee price range from 2000-01-03 to 2020-05-19?", "answer": "306.2 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0102", "question": "What was the coffee price range from 2000-01-03 to 2002-05-16?", "answer": "126.0 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0103", "question": "What was the coffee price range from 2000-01-03 to 2020-10-07?", "answer": "306.2 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0104", "question": "What was the coffee price range from 2000-01-03 to 2000-12-05?", "answer": "126.0 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0105", "question": "What was the coffee price range from 2000-01-03 to 2011-07-13?", "answer": "306.2 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0106", "question": "What was the coffee price range from 2000-01-03 to 2011-03-09?", "answer": "294.7 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0107", "question": "What was the coffee price range from 2000-01-03 to 2000-03-28?", "answer": "126.0 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0108", "question": "What was the coffee price range from 2000-01-03 to 2012-04-04?", "answer": "306.2 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0109", "question": "What was the coffee price range from 2000-01-03 to 2019-03-01?", "answer": "306.2 USD"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0110", "question": "On how many days from 2000-01-03 to 2017-07-27 did the coffee price close higher than the opening price?", "answer": "2126"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0111", "question": "On how many days from 2000-01-03 to 2009-08-07 did the coffee price close higher than the opening price?", "answer": "1224"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0112", "question": "On how many days from 2000-01-03 to 2012-07-23 did the coffee price close higher than the opening price?", "answer": "1564"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0113", "question": "On how many days from 2000-01-03 to 2007-04-19 did the coffee price close higher than the opening price?", "answer": "943"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0114", "question": "On how many days from 2000-01-03 to 2012-12-10 did the coffee price close higher than the opening price?", "answer": "1603"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0115", "question": "On how many days from 2000-01-03 to 2018-02-26 did the coffee price close higher than the opening price?", "answer": "2188"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0116", "question": "On how many days from 2000-01-03 to 2005-05-31 did the coffee price close higher than the opening price?", "answer": "694"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0117", "question": "On how many days from 2000-01-03 to 2013-11-11 did the coffee price close higher than the opening price?", "answer": "1706"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0118", "question": "On how many days from 2000-01-03 to 2016-12-14 did the coffee price close higher than the opening price?", "answer": "2064"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0119", "question": "On how many days from 2000-01-03 to 2007-11-06 did the coffee price close higher than the opening price?", "answer": "1018"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0120", "question": "What was the average percentage change in coffee price from 2017-06-02 to 2020-10-19?", "answer": "-0.2%"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0121", "question": "What was the average percentage change in coffee price from 2000-04-27 to 2011-09-14?", "answer": "0.1%"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0122", "question": "What was the average percentage change in coffee price from 2016-04-19 to 2021-10-14?", "answer": "-0.2%"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0123", "question": "What was the average percentage change in coffee price from 2009-08-13 to 2011-10-05?", "answer": "-0.0%"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0124", "question": "What was the average percentage change in coffee price from 2008-09-08 to 2022-01-31?", "answer": "-0.1%"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0125", "question": "What was the average percentage change in coffee price from 2007-01-31 to 2018-10-16?", "answer": "-0.1%"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0126", "question": "What was the average percentage change in coffee price from 2003-07-18 to 2012-12-14?", "answer": "0.0%"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0127", "question": "What was the average percentage change in coffee price from 2015-04-10 to 2017-04-11?", "answer": "-0.1%"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0128", "question": "What was the average percentage change in coffee price from 2019-08-08 to 2020-06-11?", "answer": "-0.3%"}
{"qid": "hard-coffee-0129", "question": "What was the average percentage change in coffee price from 2022-02-17 to 2022-06-08?", "answer": "-0.1%"}
